A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.38 (A2013) FA473
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.38 (A2013)
1958-2013
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA473
510.9 Cubic Feet 390 standard record storage boxes. Including but not limited to: Boxes R3989-R4003, R4011-R4385.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2013.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 20 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply.
Scope and Contents
Grant administration files and related materials.
- AC.2013.025 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2010; AC_2013_025; 18.78 Cubic Feet
  - Separated Materials, 2013:025:003-005 (Box SF 2)
  - Southeast Asia, SE; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 SE 003 - PRINCE OF SONGKLA UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - CONFERENCE ON CURRENT SOCIAL TRANSFORMATION, 2001-2005 (Box R4004)
    - 2013:025:001 - Dynamic Diversity in Southern Thailand - Library [ISBN: 974-9575-82-2]
    - 2001 SE 006 - CHIANG MAI UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - GLOBALIZATION AND POVERTY, 2001-2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2013:025:002 - Social Challenges for the Mekong Region - Library [ISBN: 974-4800-42-9]
    - 2001 SE 010 - ASIA PACIFIC FORUM ON WOMEN, LAW AND DEVELOPMENT (THAILAND) - WORKSHOP ON IDENTITY-BASED POLITICS AND IMPACT ON WOMEN, 2001-2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2002 SE 003 - KHON KAEN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - NEEDS ASSESSMENT OF EDUCATIONAL INSTITUTIONS IN CAMBODIA, 2002-2004 (Box R4004)
    - 2002 SE 016 - HANOI SCHOOL OF PUBLIC HEALTH (VIETNAM) - COLLABORATION IN PUBLIC HEALTH BETWEEN VIETNAM AND LAOS, 2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2002 SE 019 - MAE FAH LUANG UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - ROLE OF HIGHER EDUCATION IN DEVELOPING HUMAN RESOURCES IN GMS, 2002-2004 (Box R4004)
    - 2013:025:004 - The Regional Seminar on The Role of Higher Education on HRD int eh GMS Countries, November 17-19, 2003 - Library
    - 2002 SE 022 - HUE UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE AND FORESTRY (VIETNAM) - NATIONAL NETWORK ON UPLAND NATURAL RESOURCE MANAGEMENT, 2002-2004 (Box R4004)
    - 2002 SE 026 - RAJAMANGALA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - FORGING LINKAGES AMONG CAMBODIAN, THAI AND LAO AGRICULTURAL INSTITUTIONS, 2002-2004 (Box R4004)
    - 2003 SE 003 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR SOCIAL SCIENCES AND HUMANITIES OF VIETNAM - CONFERENCE ON OPPORTUNITIES AND CHALLENGES IN MEKONG SUB-REGION (Box R4004)
  - Special Programs, SP; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2001 SP 105 - (SPECIAL PROGRAMS) - BC CONFERENCE: COMMUNICATION FOR SOCIAL CHANGE STRATEGY DEVELOPMENT REVIEW, 2001-2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2001 SP 110 - WORLDSPACE FOUNDATION - AFRICA LEARNING CHANNEL, 2001-2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2001 SP 202 - CHRISTIAN COMMISSSION FOR DEVELOPMENT IN BANGLADESH - STUDY ON DEVELOPMENT IN BANGLADESH, 2001-2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2001 SP 216 - IOWA PUBLIC TELEVISION - DOCUMENTARY ON LIFE OF HENRY A. WALLACE, 2001-2005 (Box R4004)
    - 2013:025:003 - Henry Wallace, Iowa Public Radio - Digital
    - 2001 SP 304 - ARIZMENDI, DAVID - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2001 SP 305 - AUTIN, DIANA MTK - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2001 SP 306 - BAILEY, DEIRDRE LYNN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4004)
    - 2001 SP 307 - BALDWIN, GWENN A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 308 - BLACK, ANDREA G. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 309 - CHASE, JOANN K. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 310 - COLMENAR, RAYMOND A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2004 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 311 - DESANTIS, MARGARET - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM (RESCINDED) (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 312 - GONZALES, MOISES - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 313 - GRIFFITH, MARK W. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 314 - HANTZOPOULOS, EVIE - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 315 - KLEIN, MATTHEW - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 316 - LEU, JANE C. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 317 - MUHAMMAD, DAVID L. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM (RESCINDED) (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 318 - ZAR NI - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 319 - NICKENS, RUDOLPH W., JR. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 320 - PAUL, SHAUN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 321 - PERKINS, JANET L. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 322 - SAUCEDO, RENEE M. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 323 - SMALL, GAIL - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM (RESCINDED) (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 324 - STOUT, JON A. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 325 - UNO, ROBERTA J. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 326 - WARREN, ALVIN H. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 327 - YOUNGBLOOD, JOSEPH II - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 328 - DAVIS, ALFREDDIE H. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 329 - HOROWITZ, JULIE H. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 330 - SON MINH LE - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2001-2003 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 334 - ASIAN IMPROV ARTS - AMERICAN GENERATIONS RESIDENCY PROJECT, 2001-2002 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 338 - COLEMAN ADVOCATES FOR CHILDREN AND YOUTH - NETWORKS TO STRENGTHEN CIVIC PARTICIPATION AND DEMOCRACY, 2001-2004 (Box R4005)
    - 2001 SP 501 - ARAB-AMERICAN FAMILY SUPPORT CENTER - RESPOND TO IMPACT OF THE WTC ATTACK, 2001-2003 (Box R4006)
    - 2001 SP 508 - SOUTH ASIAN YOUTH ACTION - September 11th: PEACE AND UNITY INITIATIVE, 2001-2003 (Box R4006)
  - Working Communities, WC; 6.57 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - 2000 WC 029 - LEARNING COMMUNITIES NETWORK, INC. - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1995-2006 (Box R4006)
    - 2013:013:005 - LCN Overheads 57 - Digital item, 1998 June (Box R4006)
    - 2000 WC 029 - LEARNING COMMUNITIES NETWORK, INC. - GENERAL SUPPORT - Supplementary Material, 1995-2006 (Box R4006)
    - 2000 WC 031 - BARELAS COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION - ALBUQUERQUE CITYWIDE REDEVELOPMENT PLAN, 2000-2006 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 042 - PROGRESSIVE TECHNOLOGY PROJECT - CASE STUDY SUPPORT, 2000-2003 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 071 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - FOR-PROFIT TEMPORARY AGENCIES AND THE LOW-SKILLED LABOR MARKET (CHAPEL HILL), 2000-2004 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 078 - URBAN INSTITUTE - NEIGHBORHOOD JOBS INITIATIVE, 1996-2003 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 089 - CENTER FOR LAW AND SOCIAL POLICY - LOW-WAGE WORKING FAMILIES AND UNEMPLOYED ADULTS; IMPROVE WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT SERVICES, 2000-2003 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 101 - CORPORATION FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING - STRENGTHEN HOUSING-BASED EMPLOYMENT SERVICES FOR TENANTS OF SUPPORTIVE HOUSING, 2000-2006 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 111 - INTERNATIONAL LABOUR ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - WORKSHOP ON MIGRANT WORKER REMITTANCES AND MICROFINANCE, 2000-2004 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 113 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT VENTURE CAPITAL ALLIANCE - VENTURE CAPITAL AND BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT FOR THE DISADVANTAGED, 1998-2003 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 118 - NATIONAL HOUSING DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION - SEED CAPITAL FOR AFFORDABLE HOUSING PRESERVATION, 2001-2004 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 138 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - DOCUMENT CALIFORNIA ENDOWMENT-RF PROGRAM; JOINT TRUSTEE LEARNING AGENDA, 2001 (Box R4007)
    - 2001 WC 006 - CONSENSUS ORGANIZING INSTITUTE (COI) - CORE SUPPORT, 1994-2003 (Box R4007)
    - 2001 WC 023 - (BASIC RIGHTS STABILIZATION PROGRAM), 1999-2005 (Box R4007)
    - 2001 WC 028 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT VENTURE CAPITAL ALLIANCE - NEW HORIZONS FOR WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT PROJECT, 1999-2003 (Box R4007)
    - 2000 WC 132 - (INITIATIVE TO INCREASE EMPLOYMENT FOR INNER-CITY RESIDENTS), 1993-2002 (Box R4008)
    - 2013:025:006 - "A partnership for a Forgotten San Francisco" Yes on D and F; Jack Davis and Associates-Paul Kinney Prouductions - Audiovisual
      Conditions Governing Access
      Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - 2013:025:007 - Work First; How to Implement an Employment-Focused Approach to Welfare Reform Library
    - 2000 WC 132 - INITIATIVE TO INCREASE EMPLOYMENT FOR INNER-CITY RESIDENTS - Supplementary Material, 1993-2002 (Box R4008)
    - 2000 WC 132 - INITIATIVE TO INCREASE EMPLOYMENT FOR INNER-CITY RESIDENTS - Supplementary Material, 1993-2002 (Box R4009)
    - 2013:025:008 - RF 96026 - 32 color slides Still Image (Box SF 2)
    - 2001 WC 034 - JOBS FOR THE FUTURE - ACCELERATING ADVANCEMENT TO SELF-SUFFICIENCY INITIATIVE; FUND FOR THE FUTURE CORE ACTIVITIES, 2001-2003 (Box R4009)
    - 2001 WC 038 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - NONPROFIT MANAGEMENT PROGRAM, 1999-2004 (Box R4009)
    - 2001 WC 044 - URBAN INSTITUTE - WORKERS AND FIRMS IN THE LOW-WAGE LABOR MARKET, 2001-2003 (Box R4009)
    - 2001 WC 048 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - EFFECTS OF AFFORDABLE HOUSING ON FAMILIES AND CHILDREN, 2001-2005 (Box R4009)
    - 2001 WC 049 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - U.S. BUSINESS ASSOCIATIONS AND WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT PLANNING, 2001-2004 (Box R4009)
    - 2001 WC 051 - CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - DEMOCRACY STUDY PROJECT, 2000-2004 (Box R4010)
    - 2001 WC 057 - BACON, DAVID - EXPERIENCES AND PROBLEMS IMMIGRANTS FACE IN THE U.S., 2001-2004 (Box R4010)
    - 2001 WC 059 - CENTER FOR POLICY ALTERNATIVES - WORK AND FAMILY INVESTMENT INITIATIVE, 1997-2004 (Box R4010)
    - 2013:025:009 - 2003 Progressive Agenda: A Blueprint for the States - Library
    - 2001 WC 061 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - NEIGHBORHOOD NEEDS AND RESOURCES PROJECT, 2001-2005 (Box R4010)
    - 2013:025:010 - The Center for Community Problem Solving Reentry Guide - Library [ISBN: 0-9767677-0-8]
    - 2001 WC 077 - HIGHLANDER RESEARCH AND EDUCATION CENTER - PROGRESSIVE SOLUTIONS FOR SOCIAL PROBLEMS, 2001-2003 (Box R4010)
    - 2001 WC 086 - YALE UNIVERSITY - STUDY OF IMMIGRANT STUDENTS IN COMMUNITY SCHOOLS, 2000-2003 (Box R4010)
    - 2001 WC 089 - NATIONAL NEWSPAPER PUBLISHERS ASSOCIATION FUND - BLACK PRESS USA NETWORK, 2001-2002 (Box R4010)
    - 2001 WC 092 - CORPORATION FOR ENTERPRISE DEVELOPMENT - INDIVIDUAL DEVELOPMENT ACCOUNT STRATEGIC INITIATIVES, 2001-2003 (Box R4010)
    - 2001 WC 098 - NATIONAL ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND LAW CENTER - EMPLOYMENT AND HEALTH PROGRAMS IN VARIOUS CITIES, 2001-2010 (Box R4010)
    - 2001 WC 106 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - PRIVATIZATION IN NEW YORK CITY'S CHARTER SCHOOL MOVEMENT, 1999-2005 (Box R4010)
- AC.2013.054: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1999-2009; AC_2013_054; 17.03 Cubic Feet 13 standard record storage boxes, R4048-R4060; 13 standard record storage boxes, R4048-R4385
  - Working Communities (WC), AC_2013_054_1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2004 WC 148 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - ISSUES RELATED TO OFFSHORING, 2004-2006 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 149 - COMMUNITY VOICES HEARD - ANALYTIC NARRATIVE OF ITS ESTABLISHMENT AND GROWTH, 2004-2006 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 151 - WHEELING JESUIT UNIVERSITY - GENERAL SUPPORT FOR APPALACHIAN INSTITUTE, 2002-2012 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 152 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - EVALUATION OF BUILDING MIXED INCOME COMMUNITIES AREA OF WORK, 2004-2006 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 153 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - INFORMATION EXCHANGE WEBSITE, 2004-2005 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 300 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2004-2007 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 301 - BARAT EDUCATION FOUNDATION - DEMOCRACY THROUGH DIVERSITY INITIATIVE, 2003-2006 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 302 - INSTITUTE FOR COMMUNITY LEADERSHIP - INTERGENERATIONAL CROSS-CULTURAL FAMILY JUSTICE PROJECT, 2003-2005 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 303 - MENTORING CENTER - JUVENILE JUSTICE PROJECT, 2004-2006 (Box R4048)
    - 2004 WC 304 - STONE CIRCLES - SEEDING A MOVEMENT IN SUSTAINABLE ACTIVISM PROJECT, 2003-2005 (Box R4048)
    - 2005 WC 003 - COLLINS CENTER FOR PUBLIC POLICY - FUNDERS' NETWORK FOR SMART GROWTH AND LIVABLE COMMUNITIES, 2000-2007 (Box R4048)
    - 2005 WC 005 - URBAN INSTITUTE - MOVING TO OPPORTUNITY PROGRAM, 2004-2006 (Box R4048)
    - 2005 WC 006 - URBAN INSTITUTE - HOPE VI STUDY, 2001-2006 (Box R4048)
    - 2005 WC 007 - BRANDON ROBERTS AND ASSOCIATES - WORKING POOR FAMILIES PROJECT, 2003-2006 (Box R4048)
    - 2005 WC 009 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - EVALUATE WORKING COMMUNITIES' SCHOOL FINANCE GRANTMAKING IN NEW YORK STATE, 2002-2006 (Box R4049)
    - 2005 WC 011 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SANTA CRUZ - NEW YORK CITY'S NEW TEACHER INDUCTION INITIATIVE, 2004-2009 (Box R4049)
    - 2005 WC 014 - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS, AUSTIN - WATERGATE PAPERS ARCHIVE, 2005-2006 (Box R4049)
    - 2005 WC 016 - STRATEGIC CONCEPTS IN ORGANIZING AND POLICY EDUCATION - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1999-2008 (Box R4049)
    - 2005 WC 018 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - ADEQUATE SCHOOL FINANCING, 2004-2006 (Box R4049)
    - 2005 WC 019 - CEOS FOR CITIES - NEW DYNAMICS PROJECT (1 and 1 SUPPL.), 2002-2007 (Box R4049)
    - 2005 WC 020 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - DIVERSITY, IMMIGRATION, INEQUALITY AND SOCIAL CAPITAL, 2005-2008 (Box R4049)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, AC_2013_054_120; 14.41 Cubic Feet 11 record storage boxes
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Accelerating Product Development and Ensuring Product Access for Diseases of Poverty: The Role of Public-Private Partnerships in Developing Countries, 2003-2005 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Access and Equity in Higher Education: Comparative Perspectives, 2008 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Applying the World Health Organization Roadmap for End-of-life Care in Diverse Health Care Systems, 2003-2005 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Bellagio Advisory Committee, 2003-2004 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Beyond the Toolkit: Rethinking the Paradigm of Transitional Justice, 2005-2007 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Black in a White World: A Comparative Analysis of Young Men of African Descent Living in Western Nations, 2003-2005 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Blueprint for Sustaining Global Fisheries, 2005-2007 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Broadening Notions of AIDS Treatment and Care, 2004-2005 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Broadening Philanthropic Support for Racial Justice: Building Deeper Partnerships and Collaborations among Funders, 2003-2005 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Building Alliances for Global Organizing on Issues of Gender-based Violence: Working through Chasms, Differences and Boundaries, 2003-2006 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Building on Pilot Experiences to Mainstream Payments for Watershed Services as a Tool for Sustainable Conservation and Development, 2006-2007 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Building Sustainable Enterprises for the Poor: Best Practices and Lessons for the Field, 2004-2005 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Caribbean Literature Archive, 2003-2004 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Catalizing the Change Process In African Agricultural Education, 2007 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Challenges for Science in Muslim Countries, 2005-2007 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Child Development from a Global Perspective: Lost Potential, Modifiable Risk Factors, Successful Programs, and Future Goals, 2006-2007 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Collaborative Approaches to Global Communications Policy Research and Reform, 2005-2006 (Box R4050)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Collaborative Writing on Translocal Flows in the Americas, 2003-2005 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Comparative Politics: Rationality, Culture, and Structure, 2005-2006 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Concept of Freedom in the Work of Jean-Jacques Rousseau, 2005-2007 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Conceptualizing Effective and Efficient Adaptation Policies to Climate Change in Bangladesh, 2008 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Conservation of Crop Genetic Resources in the Face of Climate Change, 2007-2008 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Construction of Gender in Educational Policies: Latin American Cross-national Perspectives, 2004-2005 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Consultation on Quiet Diplomatic Regional Conflict Prevention: Towards New Institutional Arrangements, 2003-2005 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Cooperation Across Ideological Lines in the Middle East, 2004-2005 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Core eHealth technologies: mHealth and Mobile Telemedicine, 2008 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Cosmopolitan and Vernacular: The Politics of Language in the Diglossic Literary Culture of Korea, 2003-2004 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Country Experiences and Challenges for Primary Health Care, 2007 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Crop Ferality and Volunteerism: A Threat to Food Security in the Transgenic Era, 2003-2005 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Definition, Assessment, Assurance, and Improvement of Quality of Health Care in Developing Nations, 2008-2009 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Democratic Institutions and Processes and Civil War, 2003-2005 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Democratizing Women: NGOs, Empowerment and Marginalization in the 21st Century, 2003-2005 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Designing a New Entity for Impact Evaluation: A Meeting of the Leading Edge Group, 2006-2007 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Developing a Research Design for the Comparative Analysis of Strategies to Transform Poor Urban Neighborhoods, 2005-2006 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Development of Applications of Genomics in Discovery of Drugs for Tropical Diseases, 2004-2005 (Box R4051)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Development of Global Accreditation for Pediatric Pain Care, 2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Dialogues on Migration: Migration and Development - A View from Sending Countries, 2006 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Dissemination of New Technologies for Small-holder Farmers in the Developing World, 2004-2006 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Distortions to Agricultural Incentives in Developing Countries, 2005-2007 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Editorial/Dissemination Team: Cambridge General Economic Survey of Africa, 2004-2005 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: eHealth Summer Series planning meeting, 2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Empire and Modern Political Thought, 2004-2005 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Ensuring Space Security, 2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Entomopathogenic Fungi in Sustainable Agriculture: use against insects and beyond, 2007-2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Establishing a Global Program for Combating Cysticercosis, 2003-2004 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Ethical Issues in Public Health Policy in Post-Soviet Countries: Changing Attitudes and Practices towards Respect and Autonomy, 2005-2006 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Ethics Meets the Marketplace: "Best Practices" in Public-Private Partnerships to Adapt Animal and Agricultural Biotechnology to the Needs and Conditions of the Developing World, 2004-2006 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: EUROMED Sustainable Community Connections: Thematic Partnership Network, 2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Evolution of Microbial Heterogeneity and Complexity, 2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Existence of Global Values Explored through National Constitutional Jurisprudence, 2007-2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Expanding Global Philanthropy to Reach Vulnerable and Underserved GLBT Populations, 2007-2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Expanding the Frontiers of Medical Education, 2008 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Exploratory Executive Session on Technological Development and Health Care in Europe, 2003-2005 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Facing the Increase of Risk Behaviors in Adolescents through Family Protection, 2005-2006 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Family Law and Religious Law in the Abrahamic Faiths, 2003-2004 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Federalism and Subnational Constitutions: Design and Reform, 2002-2004 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Finding the African Voice: Narratives of Slavery and Enslavement, 2006-2007 (Box R4052)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: First Decade of the International AIDS Vaccine Initiative: Lessons Learned and Future Directions for a Rockefeller Foundation Experiment in the Initiation of Product Development Public/Private Partnerships in Health, 2006-2007 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Forging a Transatlantic Consensus on the Legal Rules and Institutions Governing the Use of Force by Nation States, 2004-2005 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Fostering Post-Conflict Economic Recovery, 2006 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: From Pilot Projects to Policies and Programs: Scaling up Innovations in Health Service Delivery, 2003-2005 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Gender, Globalization and Governance, 2005-2006 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Genetics Knowledge for Population Health, 2004-2006 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Girl Mothers in Fighting Forces and Their Children in Northern Uganda and Sierra Leone/Liberia: Action Research to Improve Their Situations (2006), 2005-2006 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Girl Mothers in Fighting Forces and Their Post-war Reintegration in Southern and Western Africa (2005), 2004-2005 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Alliance for Access to Public Intellectual Property in Agriculture, 2005-2006 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Intellectual Property: Designing Regional Genetic Resource Policies that Promote Food Security in Africa, 2004 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Intellectual Property: Intellectual Property and Sustainable Development - Revising the Agenda in a New Context, 2005-2006 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Intellectual Property: Open Source Models for Collaborative Innovation in the Life Sciences, 2005 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Islam and the West: Islam in Southeast Asia and Africa - Recentering the Periphery, 2005-2006 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Islam and the West: Owning the Agenda - Women's Rights in the Middle East, 2006-2007 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Islam and the West: The Challenge of Arab Reform - Whose Agenda?, 2005 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Transitional Justice: Human Rights and Transitional Justice in Iraq, 2004-2005 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Transitional Justice: Transitional Justice and Gender, 2004-2005 (Box R4053)
    - 120 - CONFERENCE: Global Dialogues on Transitional Justice: Transitional Justice in Africa - Future Directions, 2003-2004 (Box R4053)